Need a miracle?
Good Fortune is a comedy, fantasy film directed by Aziz Ansari.
A well-meaning but rather inept angel named Gabriel meddles in the
lives of a struggling gig worker and a wealthy capitalist.
Gabriel, played by Keanu Reeves.
Arj / Delivery Robots (voice), played by Aziz Ansari.
Jeff, played by Seth Rogen.
Elena, played by Keke Palmer.
Martha, played by Sandra Oh.
Linda, played by Sherry Cola.
Good Fortune is a 2025 American comedy-drama film written and
directed by Aziz Ansari in his feature directorial debut.
Seth Rogen, Ansari, Keke Palmer, Sandra Oh and Keanu Reeves star in the film.
It is produced by Garam Films, Oh Brudder
Productions, Keep Your Head, and Yang Pictures.
It follows an angel named Gabriel (Reeves), whose failed attempt to show Arj (Ansari), a struggling man, that money does not solve one's problems—by body swapping
him with his wealthy employer Jeff (Rogen)—results in Gabriel losing his wings, while the work he did as an angel begins to unravel around them.
After the suspension of his original directorial debut Being Mortal at Searchlight
Pictures in 2022, Ansari moved forward with plans to direct Good Fortune.
He wanted to make a comedy to be released in theaters, citing the success of
Barbie (2023) as proof of the viability of such a project.
Ansari's longtime friend Rogen, who inspired several elements of the
film, joined shortly after Being Mortal was shelved.
The film was set to begin principal photography in May 2023, but due to a production shutdown in the middle of the month due to the
2023 Writers Guild of America strike, filming started in late January 2024 in Los Angeles, when Palmer joined the cast.
The majority of filming wrapped before April 2024, with some scenes picked up later
after an injury Reeves sustained two weeks into filming had healed.
Good Fortune premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 6, 2025,
and was released in the United States on October 17, 2025 by Lionsgate.
The film received positive reviews from critics, and has earned
over $26 million against a budget of $30 million.
The tone is lighthearted.